krazydad.com 2018-11-14

# Krazydad Privacy Policy

**What information do I collect?**

I collect information from you when you contact me, via the contact form, or donate to the site, via PayPal. 

In both cases I may obtain your name and e-mail address. Paypal asks for additional information which I do not collect. You may, however, visit my site anonymously.

For more information about PayPal's privacy policies, see [Privacy Policy webpage](https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US).

Until January of 2018, I ran ads from Google on the website. I no longer run ads on most of the site, however I still run ads on the interactive (online) puzzles. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Krazydad. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy website](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

**What do I use your information for?**

I use your name and email solely so that I can contact you back, for example, to write thank you notes. I will not sell, exchange, transfer, or give your information to any other company for any reason whatsoever. 

**How do I protect your information?**

Paypal implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you make a donation.

All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. For more information about PayPal's privacy policies, see [Privacy Policy webpage](https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US). 

**Do I use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

I use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and to compile aggregate data about site traffic, puzzle popularity, and site interaction so that I can improve the visitor experience on the site in the future. 

**Do I disclose any information to outside parties?**

Heck no! I do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because I value your privacy I have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. I therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

I am in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). I do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. My website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

This policy was last modified on 2/21/2012

**Contacting Me**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact me using the email address below. 

dad@krazydad.com 

* * *

Copyright © 2018 by KrazyDad. All Rights Reserved.  
Privacy Policy
